pokerstars.tv 2011-01-03

# Privacy Policy on PokerStars.tv

Your privacy on the Internet is very important to PokerStars and its owner and operator, Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us from this site, by safeguarding it utilizing the best in class software and hardware architecture, techniques, methods and procedures.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard information relating to you and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

• What information is collected and for what purpose

• Confidentiality

• Limits of Confidentiality

• Who receives your information?

• Your rights in relation to your information

• Cookies

• Consent to Privacy Policy

• Who are we?

**1\. What information is collected and for what purpose**

In order use interactive features on this site, we will ask you to provide certain personal information, including a name, e-mail address, your date of birth, gender and country of residence (“Personal Information”). We will use your Personal Information to occasionally send you information on news, events, our promotions, products and services and, possibly, information about products and services of third parties carefully selected by us. If you no longer wish to receive this information, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in the correspondence we send you.

**2\. Confidentiality**

We undertake substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the Personal Information we hold about you and will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside PokerStars, other than to the Player or as described in this Privacy Policy. PokerStars has made a substantial investment in its server, database, backup, firewall and encryption technologies to protect the information collected by PokerStars. These technologies are deployed as part of state of the art security architecture.

All PokerStars employees are required to comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy provides that employees are obligated to keep Player information strictly confidential. This obligation continues once an employee has left our Company.

**3\. Limits of Confidentiality**

Legally Required Disclosures: Due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, PokerStars may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information about our Players. PokerStars will use its best reasonable efforts to limit such disclosure to the following: where PokerStars believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena, warrant or other legal process; or where reasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce PokerStars’ rights. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information to third party agents of PokerStars as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity or activity that may expose us to legal liability.

**4\. Who receives your information?**

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in Section 4 above, we may disclose your Personal Information to our employees, employees of other companies related to or affiliated with Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited and to third party service providers who use your Personal Information to provide services to us. All recipients of your Personal Information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your personal information private at no less a level than that by which we are bound.

**5\. Your rights in relation to your information**

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your Personal Information and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Where appropriate, you may have your personal information erased, rectified, amended or completed. In order to contact us regarding your information please e-mail [support@pokerstars.tv](mailto:support@pokerstars.tv) We may levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration regarding any request made by you in this regard.

**6\. Cookies**

We may send you a temporary cookie when you visit [www.PokerStars.tv](http://www.pokerstars.tv/) website. A cookie is a text-only string of information that we place in your computer’s cookie file so that we can remember who you are when you revisit [www.PokerStars.tv](http://www.pokerstars.tv/) website. We may use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept the cookie from us and you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. Please see www.cookiecentral.com/faq if you require any further information about the placing, use or deletion of cookies.

**7\. Consent to Privacy Policy**

By submitting your Personal Information to us to use interactive features, you agree to the terms of this PRIVACY POLICY. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy and encourage you to periodically review it. Your continued use of the PokerStars.tv services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

**8\. Who are we?**

Rational Entertainment Enterprises Limited, 10 Hill Street, Douglas, Isle of Man

Privacy Policy last revised: 28th September, 2004
